<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/PorcelainThroneWaterfalls/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/PorcelainThroneWaterfalls/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-11-20T18:50:05+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/PorcelainThroneWaterfalls/</id><title type="html">Porcelain Throne Waterfalls</title><subtitle>Meaningless, yet it exists. Just like you :).</subtitle><entry><title type="html">New Direction</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/PorcelainThroneWaterfalls/2017/10/26/New-beginnings/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New Direction" /><published>2017-10-26T21:14:00+03:00</published><updated>2017-10-26T21:14:00+03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/PorcelainThroneWaterfalls/2017/10/26/New-beginnings</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/PorcelainThroneWaterfalls/2017/10/26/New-beginnings/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;…dary!&lt;/em&gt; LEGENDARY! Hello to my fans. For all of you who thought that I finished my previous post with &lt;em&gt;legen…&lt;/em&gt;, I didn’t. So if that thought crossed your mind even for a second I won. You hear me &lt;strong&gt;I WON&lt;/strong&gt;. There’s a new serif in town; his name is Albert and he good at his job. Where did you think this would go? I am in control - &lt;em&gt;You&lt;/em&gt; have no power here. You lost it all when you followed that link. You don’t know me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s been such a long time since the last time I did this. Back then Donald Trump running for president was a joke. Well… Who’s laughing now? I guess it &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; still a joke somehow; one of the sad ones. The ones that make people smile out of sympathy. It’s just too awkward I guess.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I decided to write again. Actually I have been writing stuff here an there so now I should be able to compile some posts faster, which will not happen in the end. Reading back to what I wrote half a year ago, it feels very outdated and barely &lt;em&gt;me&lt;/em&gt;, so I decided to let them live in the digital notebooks unpublished, only for me and Google to read :).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having published and unpublished work feels cool I ain’t gon’ lie. To make the decision that some stuff, that you worked on once, are not worthy to &lt;em&gt;leave and live&lt;/em&gt;. I am one step closer to Damien Rice. You know, if you exclude the parts where he’s actually talented and famous and important and stuff. Maybe we’ll get there. Someday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I made &lt;em&gt;this&lt;/em&gt;. I refer to my blog, the &lt;em&gt;Porcelain Throne Waterfalls&lt;/em&gt;. It’s more of a project but also a great excuse when people ask me about this blog. See for yourself:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I really wanted to make a static website using Jekyll and host it on Github Pages. Yes this is hosted on a public github repository that you can visit and check out. Interesting huh?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here, nobody noticed my ego hiding behind my developer’s shoulders.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Nick Androulakis</name></author><summary type="html">…dary! LEGENDARY! Hello to my fans. For all of you who thought that I finished my previous post with legen…, I didn’t. So if that thought crossed your mind even for a second I won. You hear me I WON. There’s a new serif in town; his name is Albert and he good at his job. Where did you think this would go? I am in control - You have no power here. You lost it all when you followed that link. You don’t know me.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Embracing awkwardness</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/PorcelainThroneWaterfalls/2016/02/26/Embracing-awkwardness/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Embracing awkwardness" /><published>2016-02-26T00:17:00+02:00</published><updated>2016-02-26T00:17:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/PorcelainThroneWaterfalls/2016/02/26/Embracing-awkwardness</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/PorcelainThroneWaterfalls/2016/02/26/Embracing-awkwardness/">&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Embracing awkwardness like that time in a well-known fast food restaurant. GO, FLASHBACK! So, I am standing in front of the counter, waiting for my order. It is important to state that I had a to-go order; not to stay. Just for the record. I am really distracted at the moment, I don’t remember why. Aghh, I have been waiting for so long; it seems plastic food takes forever to be prepared. So I am in my happy place, singing to myself and observing people “dancing” to the music in my head #weird. As I am in front of the line, I have ahead of me disks with orders to-stay, being assembled. You know how it is; Coke comes first, the fries second while a burger or something will complete the meal. Did I say I am really distracted? I am hungry too, but that’s heavily implied. So I casually… grab a fried potato and put it in my mouth. Oh well :/. I realize what I just did and I freeze, along with the music in my head. I just took a fry from a another order #omgOmgOmg.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Brain a little help, do you mind?”
“I do mind ^^”
“Oh punny mr Brain… BEHAVE SLAVE”
“Okay, okay. You don’t have to be like that… Here’s my advice. Chew”
“Chew?”
“Ye just go with the flow, chew your potato. I mean it’s not your potato but whatever, you are not planning to spit it back into the bowl, are you?”
“I guess you’re right… There goes nothing!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I hit unpause on my imaginary boombox. ~But I’m a creeeeeeep! I’m a weirdooooooo… WHAT THE HELL AM I DOING HEEEEREEEE; I DON’T BELOOOONG HEEERE~ xD&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;In January, Geneva area is pretty dead, outdoors activities wise. So everybody does the one thing available; snowfalling. You may have heard it before by other names, such as “le snowboard” or “le ski”, but do not be fooled! It’s snowfalling. This is an interesting procedure where the amount of physical pain will clear your head from work stuff. Actually the pain is so real, it helps with stress issues. So the concept is you go on weekends. Depending on how much time you invest in snowfalling, you will get rewarded with enough pain throughout the work-week. The muscle pain may fade away by Wednesday or Thursday, but your spirit will still be crushed just in the thought of upcoming snowfalling on the slopes. This will definitely distract you from any unimportant stuff. Oh, and it was such a stress-free January ;).&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;In general, I am all for using expressions, keeping your writing, as well as your speech, interesting and diverse, however you should always use your brain. It is really important, you guys. “Use or lose it”, as my English teacher used to say. So I was with some fellow cernies, right after lunch, when one kindly asked “Would anyone fancy some coffee?”. Some of us nodded positively while others declined politely. And then there was this guy who said “Hmm coffee? Nah, it is not my cup of tea…”. Well, duh? No no. Duh doesn’t even come close to describe this. Trust me, facebook friends, this was not a troll. I was so intrigued, I had to ask. “So Blahblah” - Blahblah is not a real name, I should tell you, I made this one up; Isn’t that creative? - “What IS your cup of tea?”. The answer left me hanging. “Hot chocolate!” #facepalm&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;#realTalk. Going through stuff can take some time, but hey, time is all we got. Going through stuff alone, though, is an obstacle we can actually tackle. Thing is that most of us will not even anticipate the problem; we think we can take it. Every now and then life will troll us, tossing people in our way willing to help us out, but we are too “strong” to accept a hand. Stubborn is the word here. No one should ever go solo through anything. Even Hans had Chewbacca. All we need to solve most of our concerns is perspective! We need to embrace them and discuss them. A great song states that together sadness is half and happiness is double. And even if I heavily doubt that you can unload heartbreak and pain on others, I can assure you that you can accelerate the sad part. Then we can only hope, the next part is a happy one. So put a smile on that beautiful face of yours, go grab a friend and have a beer or two. Another song says “Use somebody”. Oh, where there’s a will, there’s a way! I will not judge :)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Reporting live from 07D -shock, I’m on a plane- and I’m about to, seriously, creep out. “Brain, are you on board?”
“I mean, technically, you are on a plane and I’m stuck with you for life, so yes!”
“Not a good time to troll mr Brain. Help me out brah!”
“l am not your brah, I am literally in your head, you dumbass. Anyhow, weirdo, you may proceed…”&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that I have the brains on my side imma gonna do the creep. I will just write the following: Hello passenger on my right. Yes, I can see your “Do not disturb” headphones, however, this is happening! You sit there all by yourself waiting. What are you waiting for? We should communicate! There is a high chance you are reading this. Is it though appropriate to read what other people write? And who is to blame if you do? I would blame your brain probably, but this is a long discussion. We should use speech; this ancient technique that we conquered as species! Come oooon neighbor. This flight is boring already, how worse can it get? Let me check my creep-o-meter… Yep, it’s over 9000. Fight back with words stranger!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Talking myself into studying these days could be easier, one would say. Let’s just say, I am pretty difficult in that respect. Assuming a random scenario, I have exams coming up for course “F”. I need to prepare to take the exam by the ancient method of “studying”; a case so unlikely in my head, I would rather castrate myself. I may be in denial, however I have to pull through this time. We don’t want to fail the F course, of course. So I take the first steps; I open the respective pdfs on my desktop, sit straight in my chair and -you know- start reading. Not a minute later, my body is shaping letters on the chair, but the weird ones; Now, I am an “S”, now a “Z” or even a “W”. Ok I agreed to study, facebook friends, not to dislocate my back. Then I have this great idea! YES! It was right there, it was so obvious; The couch. I can study from the couch. Taking the steps again; adjusting. Zoom in as needed, drag out my mouse and sit on the couch. This is so comfy, this is justice for my back. What harm would it be if I lean a little bit. Just a little bit to the arm of the couch. This could actually work! I am reading another page… Oh this couch is sooo nice, but… But putting my weight on my arm is distracting my blood flow, making it “heavy”. You know what? I should lay down completely to solve this problem. So I do, and I go on to read another page. And I scroll… And I scroll… And I scroll… And this is how I fight insomnia xD.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(•&lt;em&gt;•). ( •&lt;/em&gt;•)&amp;gt;⌐□-□. (⌐□_□)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prpp out \m/&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Nick Androulakis</name></author><summary type="html">Embracing awkwardness like that time in a well-known fast food restaurant. GO, FLASHBACK! So, I am standing in front of the counter, waiting for my order. It is important to state that I had a to-go order; not to stay. Just for the record. I am really distracted at the moment, I don’t remember why. Aghh, I have been waiting for so long; it seems plastic food takes forever to be prepared. So I am in my happy place, singing to myself and observing people “dancing” to the music in my head #weird. As I am in front of the line, I have ahead of me disks with orders to-stay, being assembled. You know how it is; Coke comes first, the fries second while a burger or something will complete the meal. Did I say I am really distracted? I am hungry too, but that’s heavily implied. So I casually… grab a fried potato and put it in my mouth. Oh well :/. I realize what I just did and I freeze, along with the music in my head. I just took a fry from a another order #omgOmgOmg.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Xmas special</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/PorcelainThroneWaterfalls/2016/01/07/Xmas-special/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Xmas special" /><published>2016-01-07T21:08:00+02:00</published><updated>2016-01-07T21:08:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/PorcelainThroneWaterfalls/2016/01/07/Xmas-special</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/PorcelainThroneWaterfalls/2016/01/07/Xmas-special/">&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;It’s been a wild Christmas period! I mean we had a new Star Wars episode in our hands so I had to prepare. So I watched 6 Star Wars in 3 days and, on the 4th day I got tickets to the latest addition to this awesome universe. I want to keep this one SPOILER FREE, so I will not actually talk at all about the movie itself or those things that were the SAME, but DIFFERENT, but STILL THE SAME… Through the whole series with all those variables, I just have to say something about a constant of this world. Original music by John Williams; Give that man a cookie! - And a hug; everybody needs one :).&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;One of my best friends, actually, made a case about the “X” in Xmas, being part of a dark marketing plot, acting like a religion variable. The concept is that Christmas needed to grow apart from Christianity, so that people would spend money regardless. Furthermore he does not accept that Xmas is just an abbreviation of Christmas, claiming that it is just an excuse xD #sureJan. Although we laugh at him, mainly because he deserves it, I have to admit he has a point; there is nothing more consumer-driven than the Santa himself. I am referring to that fat guy in red, drinking Coca Cola and sitting all day on his ass. Who the fuck is that guy anyways? And why did our parents think it was ok to let us hang around with him, let alone sit on his lap? How is all this acceptable? I mean, you would expect people to actually beat up an old guy going around singing in heavy tone anywhere close to their children. People are weird and Santa is weirder. That had to be said. Next Christmas- Xmas, whatever- do not tolerate this shit. Do not hand over your kid to Santa’s lap. Do you even realize that SANTA IS ACTUALLY AN ANAGRAM FOR SATAN? What would Jesus do? What would Oprah say? Don’t be the same-old consumer next year! You don’t have to BUY a present. You just have to BE present #deepShit.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Roundabouts again! Roundabouts everywhere in my hometown. This is not really a surprise cause you could see the signs in the past. Every new road, or reconstruction of an old one, had these perfect round thingies instead of crossroads. The surprise is that now they started to jump out frequently even downtown. I couldn’t be more happy this Xmas and I applaud whoever is behind all this! Now there’s only one thing left; my hommies need to learn how to drive. As a pedestrian crossing a roundabout you have all those zebra lines around it, which is cool. Actually that is cool only if drivers respect the zerba lines #justSayin. Let’s just hope and believe that one day the greek driver will notice the white bars on the ground and truly understand what they stand for. They stand for the simple man who just wants one thing; to cross the f*cking road in peace. I am here, waiting for you to react and sing along “Hello from the other side”. Go home Adele, you’re drunk. Nobody calls a thousand times, you creep. Get the message! Jeeeesus.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;You know it’s Christmas when you find yourself sitting on the couch with your first-degree relatives and enjoying family movies. In Greece this is literally what this holiday stands for- after the food of course- and if I had to pick a standout movie of the kind that would be “Home Alone”. To go a little bit further, I will dismiss the first ,even if that’s the original, and go straight to the sequel because it’s Xmas and you know- you’ve seen it- it takes place in snowy New York. I have two points to make. Firstly, HOW THE FUCK you forget your kid AGAIN after all the mess that occurred on the previous movie. Ok, I get it; you have a big family, but it’s the same one twice in a row. I mean dude! Don’t you think that’s a little bit suspicious? You people are so rich, you pour money down the drain. “Oh crap! I lost Kevin again. Bummer!” “It’s okay honey. Let’s throw money at the problem till it’s solved. Just book the first flight for NY on new year’s eve” #firstWorldProblems. Oh you would do everything to have Kevin in your arms once again, wouldn’t you? Other stuff like $$$ have no value compared to the divine human life. You made your point, movie, that’s enough. You want to showcase how important is Kevin to his family. Maybe- I say maaaaybe- they should not leave him back every now and then #justSayin. Now, BRAIN, take me to that second point cuz I forgot. Hmm, oh yeah! In both movies mr Culkin fights the same two burglars and in the second one they are more careful not to fall into his traps. However, because they are in another city they assume the boy will not have anything set up for them. Of course this is not the case, and Kevin fills his uncle’s place- or something- with various traps, but I will not get into that- focus- YES BRAIN. So, the kid lures the villains into position and he get on the roof from which he open the menu with the entree; bricks. BRICKS, F*CKING BRICKS! WTF? Just for the record, it was a 2-floor apartment. That takes our hero to the 3rd level a.k.a. the roof. Throwing a red brick from such height is seriously dangerous and it really shouldn’t matter who you are aiming for. He drops 4 consecutive bricks on the same target, all of them right on the forehead! Bullseye, the guy was just… dizzy. Are you serious mr family-movie-producer? Wasn’t fun enough beating up the bad guys, having them slipping on ice or falling down the stairs? Children idolize Kevin McCallister, being the badass kid who stands his ground against evil grown-ups. Is it really necessary to have him tossing bricks off the roof, getting’em headshots? Come on, mr moneymaker. Nobody wants teenagers on high-ground defending their private property. Cause in the end this actually seemed very awesome to me. Right afterwards I was craving to live my own tower defense. What was left from your little family sequel, was that no one could really get hurt by a couple of bricks in the face. Kudos! Thank god I’m out of bricks.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;This is me LIVE from a plane again -what a surprise- and I am sitting kinda in the middle of a family. To paint the picture for y’all, I have seat C and on my left is the father and the daughter, while on my right is the mother with the son. Typical cross-gender family seating #justSayin. Actually this flight is really awesome because the girl is constantly talking, ever since we fastened our seat-belts. You would expect me to be annoyed, however she is making my trip interesting enough. Reason is she is schooling her father. “Listen dad, now we are about to take off.” “Are we really?” “Yes, you don’t know it but it will happen now. Now the plane will go very very fast and after that we will be flying!”. At last, a girl that knows her shit xD. “Dad, now we are flying because the plane is like a downhill”. You know, I have to double-check that we are going upwards and not downwards because she sounds so trustworthy… Ok, check. “Cool now we are going to order food!” “Are you sure? They usually bring it to us”. “Dad! Dad, you don’t know, you will see. They are taking our order and then they cook for us in the kitchen” WAIT A MINUTE. There is a kitchen on the plane of which I am not aware! “Where is this kitchen, honey?” her dad asked kinda amused with a trollish attitude. DO YOU THINK IT’S FUNNY MISTER? Talking about an imaginary kitchen on a plane that serves yogurt every f*cking time? “Yes dad, of course there is a kitchen. Duh? It’s on the back of the plane! That’s where they prepare our orders.” OKAY BRAIN, FALSE ALARM. Put down your pitchforks, pipol! It seems that there is actually a kitchen here and we are having proper airplane food. So, basically, now I am waiting to give my order. Hmm, I think I’m having a burger. Yep, burger it is. #noooooooooot&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I am writing this last piece from my french village; yeah… back to work :/. My return to my place was interesting. I wont say I was surprised but my house was a mess. It was not dirty- well you could say that too- just things everywhere. We were accommodating friends before the holidays so we have some excuses. So let’s say the inflatable bed was still there. Then, we had some big boxes in the house, after a big thomann shipment arrived just before we left for Greece- so I unwrapped and left everything there xD. Hmm what else… And some luggage in the hallway- that are not even ours. Next to them you could find some plastic bags with leftover booze from a friends party and on the right another bag with meds this time. All of them on the floor. Some laundry to be done too. Last but not least we had this specific corner, that we call, the recycling corner. There we gather paper wrappings in a huuuuuge- like humongous huge- plastic bag in order to get them eventually to the recycling bin. Because we care about the environment, then again do we? Not the point. BRAIN what was the point here? Help me out brother. Yes, yes. Point is I should do less typing and more tiding up my ecosystem so that the living organisms inside don’t give up on life.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;You can read 4 again; It’s exactly the same B&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;tl;dr -&amp;gt; Just some thoughts in Star Wars order. You don’t have to read them. Class dismissed!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prpp out \m/&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Nick Androulakis</name></author><summary type="html">It’s been a wild Christmas period! I mean we had a new Star Wars episode in our hands so I had to prepare. So I watched 6 Star Wars in 3 days and, on the 4th day I got tickets to the latest addition to this awesome universe. I want to keep this one SPOILER FREE, so I will not actually talk at all about the movie itself or those things that were the SAME, but DIFFERENT, but STILL THE SAME… Through the whole series with all those variables, I just have to say something about a constant of this world. Original music by John Williams; Give that man a cookie! - And a hug; everybody needs one :).</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Outdated thoughts</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/PorcelainThroneWaterfalls/2015/12/24/Outdated-thoughts/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Outdated thoughts" /><published>2015-12-24T17:46:00+02:00</published><updated>2015-12-24T17:46:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/PorcelainThroneWaterfalls/2015/12/24/Outdated-thoughts</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/PorcelainThroneWaterfalls/2015/12/24/Outdated-thoughts/">&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Outdated, like the following intro. One would expect a Star Wars reference opening this one. One will be disappointed. Here you will find scattered thoughts documented as they occurred, somewhere during the past two months. Proceed at your own risk. Reader discretion advised.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Previously on Gotta Say… lol that’s too soon. This is like the fourth post and you want already to open like that? People will be like “What the f*ck is Gotta Say?” and “Why haven’t I unfriended this annoying dude yet?”. But… but I was ready to -you know- give them some intro theme music to open on another tab, while reading my epic prologue. Nobody cares bro! Maaaaybe some other time -maybe on my blog; when that’s done-. Thank god I finished Mr. Robot, cause lately I’ve been talking to myself more than I need to. I mean this guy can be a real pain in the ass.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Movember, this time of the year, when guys that don’t actually like shaving, shave. No surprise there, I mean everybody loves trends. They love the puns too, so let me think. Oh yeah “Time to shave the world”. You think that was 2ez probably. If you think about it, it is just an everyday quote for barbers. Well, I admit it was poorly designed, so let’s try one more. Hmm… “Shaving Ryan’s privates”. Even if I made me laugh, I feel like I have to elaborate, so that I don’t sound like a pervert. So, obviously it’s a reference to “Saving private Ryan”. Less obvious to most people, is that the whole Movember thing is about testicular cancer, among other things and, since “privates” is short for private parts, meaning genitals; there you have it, I’m funny -or gross, you decide- I don’t care, I could even go like “Shaving privates Ryan’s” and claim some next level Yoda syntax B  - Happy Star Wars pipol!&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Next year the section, that both me and my heart belong to, is moving to another department and group. So now we are under “Finance, Administration, Procedures” department and “Treasury, Reporting and Processes” group. Basically you can say now that I’m in the FAP department aaaand my group is a TRaP. xD Kudos and many thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I’m in the same flight as Boyz’n’Noiz. OMG OMG OMG OMG OMG OMG OMG. Actually I’ve only heard they exist once before, in a conversation with a teenager. Which makes sense, since it’s a greek teen boyband. Imagine One Direction; from Lidl. Just from the attitude I could tell they are the REAL DEAL, you know? Indoors sunglasses and stuff - the whole package. It wasn’t very hard to identify them, really. At first, I was sure, this was a boyband; pretty faces with a cool manager around. It also helped that they kept throwing their group name out in the air with stupid excuses like “We went there and it was super quiet and everyone was like hoooow can this be - Boyz’n’Noiz and no noizzzzzz”. Popstars! The good kind too. Oh, I wish I could hit that high -I don’t give a f*ck- note, but I’m too old for this shit :/&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: When I got off the plane there was a crowd gathered to welcome them to Heraklion - like 30 girls. They were setting rules “Ok so nobody will jump him and tear him apart. He belongs to all of us”. Rofl, just #rofl.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I’m stupid. I don’t intend to offend really stupid people so let’s say I feel stupid. So, I feel stupid; planning a two-days trip to Greece, with attention to detail, just to arrive in front of my house at 2AM and to realize I have no keys to access the building. I feel stupid; being in that specific moment, absolutely mad at myself already, yet to realize I forgot my coat at the bar I was an hour ago. It’s ok -no it’s not. I feel stupid; having to go to the airport to spend the night till my morning flight. I feel stupid; eating at mcdonald’s to pass the time -actually I like eating junk food, so that was time well-spent. I feel stupid; sleeping at the airport gate. To be honest I don’t believe in stupidity. Stupid me, you’re a part of me. Dummy me, you belong with me.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I have a weird relationship with airplane food. You know how airplane food is most of the times more “meh” rather than “huh”? Given the fact I’m a foodie under cover -my cover being a huge pile of delicious junk food- I should neither be interested nor impressed, however I have this thing. I need -yes, “need” is the word of choice- to eat every last thing served on the plane. Just note that I mean the portion served to me; I do not go around the plane eating other people’s food. Point is, airplane food is meant to be diverse to fill different tastes in, let’s say, breakfast. So you have some bread and butter, with some marmalade on the side. Plus you get something like scrumbled eggs and, last but not least, there is yogurt with honey. All those acompanied by orange juice and/or coffee of course. Now a normal person would there are choices to be made here; not me though. Have you met me? I ate EVERYTHING. I had coffee AND orange juice. MISTAKES WERE MADE. I feel this is part of my ticket; I paid for this food and now it is under my responsibility. What I’m sayin’ is that if don’t eat that food, no one will. I am in charge of this situation. This food will not go to waste. And what about the children starving in other places on this planet? - What about them? No no don’t go there. ENOUGH! Enough with the fake motives. Truth is I would eat the airplane wings if there was bbq sauce involved.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;“I guess the key to a lot of things is balance. Whether is balance of power. Balance in love. Or sometimes… just balance. For some of us it seems too far out of reach. Too difficult to achieve. But the important thing is just to never stop trying. Especially if you like girls named Alex… and chicken salad.” Just a great quote form Scrubs; a must-see series if you have… -you know- a soul. Of course, Alex ended up to be an addict stealing meds behind JD’s back, or something. It seems that Alex may not worth our time JD; chicken salad on the other side… Think about it! Note to self: Hunt a chicken on the way back to the village you live in. Oh, and grab mayo from the store. Chicken salad, facebook friends, the easiest thing after… -now at this point I would say “your mother” but I don’t want to sound offensive so I’m taking the high road on this one- the easiest thing after this backflip I just did while typing. How I wish you were here, then I could offer you some chicken salad.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Lately, I am taking planes regularly; at least compared to previous years. One would say that I’m pretty fly for a white guy #badJokes - couldn’t resist, I don’t care. Stay on point. YES, BRAIN. Lemme start from the top. People tend to get scared on flights and that is focused a lot on the take-off and the landing. These two phases are actually similar on a danger scale - I mean a plane either works or it doesn’t- however, the latter one is more drama-heavy. That is probably because after take-off you can’t actually just relax, since there is still the landing on the way. You are half-way there, but not there yet. So, I guess it would be fair to say that people are focusing their negative energy on the landing. So the plane is heading downwards and you are holding your breath just until the wheels touch the ground. The following seconds are crucial for you because the plane is kinda bouncing like Snoop Dogg in da hood. And then, the stress relief. You can actually hear people around you exhaling air off their lungs. You can see random smiles. I mean, I remember passengers in the past that started clapping. Wtf? This fake trust towards the pilot suddenly breaking out. Like “the take-off was ok, but you really nailed the landing! Congrats”. I noticed they don’t do that anymore. Have we become more mature as a species? Not really. I’m pretty sure everyone is still clapping in their heads.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: Guys, guys!- And grills!- Actually on my last flight people clapped when we touched the ground. Faith in humanity: Restored! B&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I was in a committee room providing tech assistance some time ago, when the mouse started to malfunction. At first, I offered my notepad as a mousepad cause the desk surface could be the issue. The user tried it and thanked me since, I guess, it made a difference. After like 10 minutes the mouse was not responding properly again. So, because it was a wireless one I assumed it had to do with that and then I noticed this thing a bit further, behind the mouse below the screen. “Oh yeah, that’s the mouse detector thingie, it’s facing the wrong direction!” I said and I stood up to reach it and reposition it to face the mouse. I was already there, having my hand over it, when I actually realized that the THINGIE was NOT a mouse detector. It was presenter; you know, a presentation pointer, that actually had a front similar to a detector, in my defence. Keeping my cool, I moved it anyway B . Now the user tried once more. “Oh thanks, Nick. That’s perfect now. You, computer guys, know everything!” she said. And no more errors occurred that day… PLACEBO MOTHERF&lt;em&gt;CKERS! IT F&lt;/em&gt;CKING WORKS xD.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S.: Papakaliatis, you scumbag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Merry Poppins&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prpp out \m/&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Nick Androulakis</name></author><summary type="html">Outdated, like the following intro. One would expect a Star Wars reference opening this one. One will be disappointed. Here you will find scattered thoughts documented as they occurred, somewhere during the past two months. Proceed at your own risk. Reader discretion advised.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Confessions of a troll</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/PorcelainThroneWaterfalls/2015/10/25/Confessions-of-a-troll/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Confessions of a troll" /><published>2015-10-25T23:52:00+02:00</published><updated>2015-10-25T23:52:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/PorcelainThroneWaterfalls/2015/10/25/Confessions-of-a-troll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/PorcelainThroneWaterfalls/2015/10/25/Confessions-of-a-troll/">&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I’ve been busy procrastinating about more important stuff than this shitpost, so because you probably don’t even care -and I don’t blame you- let’s just quote this one away; “Oh I am sorry Frodo” pause for drama “…I was delayed.”. “Well, screw you Gandalf, I almost turned into wraith” #lotrQuotes&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Maroumi and I declared this following, shared, year in Geneva as a wine tasting season, but first things first. Maria -&amp;gt; Marouli. My roommate -&amp;gt; Mah roomie -&amp;gt; Maroumi. So where was I? Oh, yes, wine. When in France, you have to understand, there’s actually lots of wine involved. Red, white, rouge; you name it. We have not yet tasted bad wine. Of course some of them are clearly better that other, setting high standards but you can get proper wine for 2-4 euros, a bottle at a supermarket. And then there are these wine tasting events every now and then… I mean a wine tasting year with inner wine tasting weekends, with wine tasting days in those too, you get the picture; It’s #wineception. Sorry beer, you have to try harder this year and fight to keep your place in my blood. 1437 Kozel. 1437 is code for “I love you forever”; a character counter. There you go, facebook friends, you get to learn something new, however not important at all :). You are welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Roundabouts; I am all about them. Seriously, a friend of mine claims I’m obsessed. But let’s be real, what’s not to like? Lemme break this down for ya’all. First of all, roundabouts are circular. Appreciate the symmetry, kid. Ok, crossroads can be symmetric too but are they, really? Most of them look like dancing ravers in the 90’s even if most of the ravers see circles anyway. Moreover, a roundabout is practical in a way. You know, in case you like it too much, you can stay there, forever lost in the moment, going around it screaming “ROUNDABOUOUOOUOUUOOUT, while fighting back the centrifugal force. And trust me when I say; the force is strong in this one  B  . But most importantly, they control traffic better than f*cking traffic lights AND THEY ARE NOT EVEN CALLED TRAFFIC ROUNDABOUTS. And why would they? There is never traffic around a roundabout -except for Ilioupoli, but that’s a bad, bad, sad implementation.- so that would be dumb. I mean you can’t just run past a roundabout and cause an accident. You have to stop #justStahp. I made my case and now I see circles. #kyrile&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I think I have developed an addiction for cheese. The variety of cheese in a french supermarket is crazy - or “it’s cray” if you are an Obama fan- and I made a vow to try everything I can. So I am not sure if it’s an addiction yet, however I do eat some cheese daily. And there are these moments in the night, I would open the fridge for bacon, but now I do that for Gruyere too. Just to be clear, I am not eating it, I am checking on it. I want to make sure that the cheese is there for me, just in case I need it, you know, at 4AM. There is, also, a high chance that Maroumi eats the Gruyere while I am fast asleep. Damn you, sleep. Damn you, Maroumi. Damn you, cheese #damn. I mentioned Gruyere once too many times now, but we have a special connection &amp;lt;3. There is a story behind how we met, but I’ll get to that later. I’ll just say that it’s the best cheese I’ve ever had, like the king of cheese(s) -or the queen; I’m not sexist- the mayor of Cheese town, like Parmigiano and Graviera had a baby -_-. Oh and it’s not french, so SUCK IT France, you and your excellent -but not good enough- cheese. Whatever, maybe I am a cheese addict, but I’m going for the fridge and there’s nothing that can stop me now haha HAHAHA-it’s actually hard to type an evil laugh :/.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Inflatable beds, hmm. At this point there was something to be said about inflatable beds -I made a note and everything- buuuut I have no f*cking clue. And that’s why you don’t just keep keywords in your notes, especially if you don’t plan to expand them sometime soon. So I’ll tell you what I remember. I am pretty sure that the origin of this note goes back to a dorm room in EPFL in early October. It probably had to do with some funny thought about either my lower back pain or the perception of flying in your sleep because of the floaty experience they offer, enabling mad movement skillz in your dreams. Thing is I might have been a little extrahappy- aka drunk, because… Lausanne- so whatever it is about inflatable beds, has a fat chance of being neither funny nor interesting at all :/. So let’s focus on my poor note keeping skillz. I’m bad. I write just random words/phrases down regarding stuff happening around me, trusting myself -Have I met me?- to remember later what it’s all about. The fact that this is the fourth bullet I am expanding, having another ten of them in gKeep, is giving me the chills. We can do this brain! I trust you. #brainTrust&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Have you seen the “Back to the future” trilogy? Yeah, me neither. However there was this event organised by CERN Cinema Club, on the 21st of October, because on this day of 2015 the main characters arrive at the future. So it’s this unique moment of a lifetime -blah blah :P- and there was this scheduled “back to the future 2” screening at a big conference room at CERN. The movie itself was neither good nor bad, but the most enjoyable part was actually the audience. Most of you may know I’m nerdy, or so I thought. People were seriously overexcited about the whole thing. You could feel the nerdgasms taking place around you and literally hear the heavy breathing involved xD. At some point, I think I saw a dude lip-syncing a whole scene of the movie; that’s some massive commitment, kudos! Maybe I am exaggerating just a bit, but these CERN employees did have much more fun than I did, clearly due to different reasons. I jelly. Nerdy me, if you read these lines, please come out and play. F*ck it, Star Wars marathon this week.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;So we are in Lausanne for a night and we are crashing in an EPFL dorm -Oh not this story again… Facebook friends trust me, I remember this one.- So we are being accommodated, Eli and me, by Bojan -a Serbian fella, friend of a friend; two times friend- and we get in the dorm at 3AM, more or less, after some beers. So we decide to go to sleep right away cause we need to wake up early in the morning and we inflate the inflatable bed- I swear this in not about the bed :P- when our host is like “Guys, do you want some Gruyere?”. “I actually never had Gruyere before” I reply, while I watch him slice the cheese that is about to blow my mind away -everywhere around the place, like little Annoula after the explosion-. AND THIS IS HOW I MET YOUR MOTHER #booooom. But actually this is not what this is about. So we get out of bed to eat Gruyere and we start chit-chatting when this girl knocks the door and starts to argue that we are too loud. Too loud on a f*cking Saturday night; I mean seriously? We don’t talk back at all and we say we’ll keep it down. Aaaand in five minutes there she is again and she is really pissed, like REALLY mad. I know when you’re drunk you may not control your audio output perfectly but we were not that loud. There is a little bit of argument this time but nothing major. We end up going to to bed after this huge buzzkill :/. We all agreed in the end it was Gruyere’s fault. Damn, Y R U so GD?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;We went to Broc to visit Callier’s chocolate factory and there was a lot of chocolate involved. During the first part of the tour, though, we did this interactive part where you walk through rooms while a narrator expla- actually I just want to talk about the narrator, the rest is neither important nor interesting. This voice was so deep and epic that it didn’t fit the whole concept. I was feeling this chocolate history experience was about to switch to middle Earth at any moment with orcs and goblins running through the walls! And every time he referred to Coco beans the earth would quake and the skies would thunder. F*cking COCO BEANS maaaan. He put those twice in every sentence at least. He started talking about chocolate and ended up with the French Revolution involved, and of course there were COCO BEANS EVERYWHERE. I started to wonder whether the whole Revolution was just a big french #sugarRush. It’s always down to Liberté, égalité, fraternité… and COCO BEANS! B&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Around here drivers tend to respect pedestrians a lot, for example waiting before zebra crossings for them to pass. You know, borderline politeness that greek drivers don’t understand. But now that I have to be one of them, I try to behave while driving. Good thing is I found this new hobby of mine. I force people to cross streets. Yes I do that. So I see three random guys standing on the pavement, just talking to each other, with clearly no intention to use the zebra crossing next to them, I just stop in front of them. I play the waiting game until they notice me. Now they think I’m too polite and they consider crossing just to avoid disappointing me -I’m totally in their heads. Most of the times people will just nod or wave a signal for me to pass, but every once in a while they will actually cross the road and offer me precious laughing tears. #Worth&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;It’s cold and sometimes it is wise for me to wear gloves. There are these days that I walk back from work and it’s like a 25-minute walk. I put on my headphones, start Spotify, skip to a song I like, put on my gloves and start walking; all those in this specific order. Most of the times there will be a really awful song on the playlist that I need to skip and here is my problem; my gloves. I can’t press shit on my touchscreen with the gloves on. So I consider my options. I can take off a glove press the “next” button and move on with my life, however due to the cold this is not optimal. Optimal would be gloves that can use a touchscreen. So I go for my second option and I start hitting my screen with my nose trying to aim for the correct button. And there I am, walking on the sidewalk, nose pecking my phone like Woody woodpecker. The first time I almost nose-dialed a friend by mistake trying to skip Taylor Swift ;She is annoying. On another occasion I hit “pause”. That’s just great… Now I have to nose-peck two buttons, to get the #starbucksLovers off my ears. Eventually I googled for these gloves above and, apparently, they exist. Thing is by that moment i was already a pro at nose-phoning. I can hit the right button, every f*cking time, now. I am seriously considering texting the same way from now on. #challengeAccepted&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PS: I had a couple more stuff to write about but this is too long already. That being said, I hope it will not take me another month to get down to writing again. Expect me. Dunno maybe next time I’ll write something about music. I’ll be Bach! xD&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;tl;dr: I know this time it is actually too long to read, but ask yourself this: What would Jesus do? Jesus would read this. But if you’re not the #randomJesusOnMyFriendlist, it’s ok for you to walk away. Pobody’s nerfect!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prpp out \m/&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Nick Androulakis</name></author><summary type="html">I’ve been busy procrastinating about more important stuff than this shitpost, so because you probably don’t even care -and I don’t blame you- let’s just quote this one away; “Oh I am sorry Frodo” pause for drama “…I was delayed.”. “Well, screw you Gandalf, I almost turned into wraith” #lotrQuotes</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Geneva 101</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/PorcelainThroneWaterfalls/2015/09/28/Geneva-101/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Geneva 101" /><published>2015-09-28T05:06:00+03:00</published><updated>2015-09-28T05:06:00+03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/PorcelainThroneWaterfalls/2015/09/28/Geneva-101</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/PorcelainThroneWaterfalls/2015/09/28/Geneva-101/">&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;According to Zipf’s law, 80% of the points you will find interesting in this post, will be found on 20% of the whole thing. Given the fact, this is a ten-bullet “Gotta Say”, you should find them, two, and move on with your lives to be time efficient. However, this is not one of them. Sorry for wasting your time :)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;You should heavily invest emotionally on some people. You just have to find them first. You don’t need a lot of them, but make sure they know their place. The rest are just buffer people, you don’t really care for. I mean you like them, however do you(?).&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Performing a search for “Tarantino soundtracks” on Spotify for the first time, could be -and maybe, should be- an #achievementUnlocked titled “It took you a while” or “You have some taste after all”. It finally occurred to me just a few weeks ago. Ever since, my new ringtone is the GoT_shame_bells and I cry myself to sleep at night. I just feel bad. Unchain my heart, Quentin, please!&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;When I ask people if they use it, most of them refer to Snapchat as the sexting app. Assuming that is the general approach, I might as well say a couple of things. I’ll start with -Yes, it is. Thing is, Snapchat can be so much more! I cannot, and definitely will not, give a lot of credit because it is a crappy, poorly designed, app imho. On the other hand, it is just for fun and is, for sure, such a creative way of expressing your everyday, meaningless, side. It has a shitload of hidden features too! Go ahead and check the semi-transparent color and stuff. Shit is cool -shit is legit. You are welcome facebook friends. #snapchatPromoPost&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Friendly shots-fired on my sister’s last #exwNaPost and now my mind is down a very dark path. I can’t stop thinking us two taking care of business on #epicRapBattlesOfHistory. I know, right? That’s crazy and even if my “history” is stronger than hers, I wish we could just change category and get the pink one. You know, the one with the tv shows and the movies. But then again that would be waaaaay2ez.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I would run five hundred miles and I would walk five hundred more to have my internet connection restored. Seriously now, those days are dark and full of terror mainly because they, always, happen to be days with a clear schedule. Like ALWAYS. Of course there are in-house alternatives. I would grab my guitar but for how long? I would eat forever but I read somewhere it’s not healthy(?). Don’t believe anything you read online. Don’t be dumb. Eat forever. Generally the only thing worse than internetlessness-yes that’s a word now, google it- is a diet. #itIsDecided&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Genetically modified food sounds scary to some people. Actually in greek modified is translated exactly the same way as mutant. Of course, eating something that hangs around in sewers and loves pizza sounds weird. Or even the other guy with the long nails coming off his fists. I’ll pass on that too, thank you very much. Of course, OF COURSE. But maaaaaybe. Maybe, it comes down to bad marketing. I mean why would you even call it genetically modified food? “Actually, it’s scien-“ Shut your face. No one appreciates a show off. I say we take some notes from Apple. No, #iFood is not that good, but what about #foods (fud-es)? Yes, like the new iPhone. Don’t you get it? The humanity was waiting for so long for this very moment. We kept food safe, as a non-countable word, for a reason. Everything now makes absolute sense. Everything is connected. #foods, it’s gonna be a thing. Remember me. This is my design.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;So there’s this study I read about, they did on a sample of 230,768 people. They did a statistical analysis and proved that when you use specific numbers on your lies you have 87.6% higher chances of making your audience believe them. Aaaand, that was one of them -_-. I just hope you dont feel abused. Not that I would care.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I’m writing these last few bullets, while I casually fly over the Alps. Yes, I just said that. Fyi, the Alps are mostly white today. Also Eddie Vedder is sad in my ear, cause his girl died in a car accident :/ ~Oh where, oh where can my baby be? The lord took her away from me. She’s gone to heaven so I got to be good so I can see my baby when I leave this world.~ This song is actually emotional gold.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;One of these days I’m gonna miss #souvlaki so much, it will haunt my dreams. I’m pretty sure, in the end, I will go down in Geneva to have one, just to disappoint my appetite cause it can be the worst souvlaki i will ever have. I’m not ready yet! Thank god, falafel is great here. I’m cheating on souvlaki with falafel, call me a #junkFoodWhore.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;tl;dr -&amp;gt; Hey Jesus! It’s me again :/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prpp out \m/&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Nick Androulakis</name></author><summary type="html">According to Zipf’s law, 80% of the points you will find interesting in this post, will be found on 20% of the whole thing. Given the fact, this is a ten-bullet “Gotta Say”, you should find them, two, and move on with your lives to be time efficient. However, this is not one of them. Sorry for wasting your time :)</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">43rd of August and counting</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/PorcelainThroneWaterfalls/2015/09/12/43rd-of-August-and-counting/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="43rd of August and counting" /><published>2015-09-12T23:44:00+03:00</published><updated>2015-09-12T23:44:00+03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/PorcelainThroneWaterfalls/2015/09/12/43rd-of-August-and-counting</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/PorcelainThroneWaterfalls/2015/09/12/43rd-of-August-and-counting/">&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Yes pipol, I will be doing this thingie, my sister does. I even copied the title just to salute her style. It’s not personal, Nassia. It’s strictly business #GodfatherQuotes. Oh, there’s no going back now #copyCat #noRegrets&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Now that I leave Greece, I get to, finally, post in english. I can always claim that I have to do it from now on, cause of my european friends, hiding the fact, I’m just a poser and a hipster, who enjoys typing in English B .&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I guess sharing music on social media is like sharing thoughts (well, #noShitSherlock). There will always be those who just get it and, of course, those who don’t. I actually enjoy listening sad music; in a way sad music balances me out. Let’s just say, pretty often “my happy is too loud” and I need to level it down xD. Point is that if you really care of what people will think of your posts, then you shouldn’t post in the first place. No, it’s not some heart-opening to strangers (sorry, facebook friends) ;it’s some taste-sharing (you’re welcome, facebook friends). After all, #sharingIsCaring.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;But, seriously, take a moment to look at the dark sky at night. Now, take a deep breath and start counting all those fucks that I give, orbiting our planet just like the Moon.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;So there’s this imaginary place near Baghdad, I will be visiting from time to time, called Donethat. Of course there’s Fuckthat just around the corner too. Damn, greek jokes sound way much cooler in greek #duh. However, I get to use #duh now, so that’s a trade I’m, kinda, okay with B .&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;And I will quote one of my sisters(I’m not throwing people under the bus) at this point: “How does gPhotos categorize my photos as food or flowers? Is there an employee, whose job is to do so?” :D :D. #howStuffWorks #blackMagic&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Everybody should know that half of my jokes are bad on purpose. -yeah ok, I like half of my bad jokes, so the other half of them. A quarter- I strongly believe in maintaining the balance in things, -the yings and the yangs, you feel me?- and I, really, would not like a black hole in my living room… and there’s another one! #Yay :/&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;To be honest, that last one made me laugh. -Shame, shame, shame… &lt;em&gt;bell dings&lt;/em&gt; #loopForever.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;There is a lot of selfishness involved in expecting people to laugh at your jokes. My rule of thumb for jokes goes like this: You should just go ahead and say anything -literally anything- that would make you laugh. Τhat being said, you should always amuse yourself with your jokes. They may be dumb. They may be pathetic excuses for jokes, but if that makes you happier, even for a moment, it should be ok. Now if you’re good enough, at times, you will make other people around you smile too. But, to be fair, that does not mean you are always funny. It means you are social though, and good for you kid. Good for you. #johnOliverStyle&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;In case you want to give feedback on this thingie, I give you this riddle to solve. “What has two thumbs and doesn’t give a crap?” Well, it’s not Sir Jaime Lannister, that’s for sure. #spoilerAlert&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Will there be an easter egg in this post? I don’t know #obviousLie. In case there is, though, the code to find it should be this one: 12~0~28~27~0~0~28~0~0~26~0. This one is easy. You are smart kids, you’ll figure it out. #nextLevel.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;tl;dr -&amp;gt; Read the damn thing, Jesus -it’s not water. you can’t just go over it-. Same thing applies to everyone, not just the #randomJesusOnMyFriendlist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prpp out \m/&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Nick Androulakis</name></author><summary type="html">Yes pipol, I will be doing this thingie, my sister does. I even copied the title just to salute her style. It’s not personal, Nassia. It’s strictly business #GodfatherQuotes. Oh, there’s no going back now #copyCat #noRegrets</summary></entry></feed>